A Finding Aid to the Stendahl Art Galleries Records, 1907-1971, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Subject Files, 1907-1971; Series 4; Archival Resource Key; 4.8 Linear feet Boxes 3-8, OV 9
  - Oakland Art Gallery, 1930; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Obata, Chiura, circa 1931; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - O'Malley, Power, 1928-1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Orozco, Jose Clemente, 1930; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Osthaus, Edmund, circa 1924; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Otis, George de Mont, 1928; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Pages, Jules, 1923-1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Paris, circa 1930; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Payne, Edgar, 1921-1931; Archival Resource Key; Oversized material housed in OV 9 (Box 6, Folder 34-35)
  - Pearson, Ralph M., Printed Material and Photographs, 1922-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Pearson, Ralph M., Artwork, circa 1922; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Pedretti, Humberto, 1924-1925; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Pfister, Jean Jacques, 1930-1932; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Pinazo, Jose Martinez, circa 1930; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Picasso, Pablo, circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Plaza Art Center, circa 1930; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Porray, Stan Pociecha, 1931; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Proctor, A. Phimister, 1923-1931; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Pushman, Hovsep, 1921-1935; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Puthuff, Hanson, 1921-1929; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Redmond, Granville, 1931-1932; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Reindel, Edna, 1939-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Remington, Frederick, 1928-1931; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Rider, Arthur, 1929-1935; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Ritschel, William, 1929-1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 6-7)
  - Rivera, Diego, 1923-1949; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Rose, Ethel, 1926-1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Rose, Ethel, 1926-1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Rose, Guy, 1927-1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Sachs, Joseph, 1948; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Schmidt, Carl, circa 1933; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Schofield, Walter Elmer, 1928-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 14-15)
  - Sexton, Fred, 1935; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Sheets, Millard, 1930-1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Shermund, Barbara, 1933; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Siqueiros, David Alfaro, 1932; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Smith, Frank Vining, 1933; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Smith, Jack Wilkinson, 1926-1930; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Soudeikine, Sergei, 1934; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Stojana, Gjura, circa 1929; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Swinnerton, James, 1928-1934; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Taggart, Richard, circa 1935; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Tauszky, David A., 1927-1930; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Terechkovitch, Kostia, circa 1937; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Thomas Gilcrease Foundation, 1946-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 28-30)
  - Vidar, Frede, circa 1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Wagoner, Harry, 1927-1930; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Waring, Brooke, circa 1935; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Warshawsky, Alexander, 1925-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Wendt, Julia Bracken, 1928-1930; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Wendt, William, circa 1926-1950; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 36-37)
  - Wendt, William, circa 1926-1950; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 1-5)
  - Wenzell, Arthur B., 1923; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - White, Orrin, 1921-1930; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Ybarra, Alfred, circa 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Zuloaga, Ignacio, circa 1925; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Oversized Payne, Edgar Material from Box 6, Folders 34-35, 1921-1928; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 9)